Lovestone, Jay Papers 6036/028
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Wittfogel, Karl, 1966-1976 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Wolfe, Bert and Ella, 1971-1981 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Wollenberg, Otto, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Wollenberg, Otto, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Wollenberg, Otto, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Wollenberg, Otto, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Wollenberg, Otto, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Wollenberg, Otto, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Wollenberg, Otto, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Wollenberg, Otto, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Wollenberg, Otto, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - X, Y, Z, (General Correspondence), 1965-1981 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - X, Y, Z, (General Correspondence), 1965-1981 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Zimmerman, Charles, 1966-1974 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Zimmerman, Charles, 1966-1974 (Box 4, Folder 93)
- Series II. Foreign Files
  - Africa, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Albania, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Argentina, 1947-1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Austria, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Austria, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Austria, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Bangladesh, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 6a)
  - Bolivia (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Brazil, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Bulgaria, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Cambodia (Box 5, Folder 9a)
  - Communist China, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - East Germany, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Egypt, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Finland, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 13a)
  - France, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 13aa)
  - Germany, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 13b)
  - India, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 13c)
  - Indonesia, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - ICFTU (Box 5, Folder 14a)
  - Israel, 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Italy (Box 5, Folder 15a)
  - Japan, 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Latin America, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 16a)
  - Middle East, 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - NATO (Box 5, Folder 17a)
  - North and South Korea, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Poland, 1970-1980 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Russia, 1929-1981 (Box 5, Folder 19a)
  - Russia, 1929-1981 (Box 5, Folder 20a)
  - South Africa, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 20b)
  - South Vietnam, 1963-1970 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Spain, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 21a)
  - Sudan, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Tanzania (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Turkey, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Vatican, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Venezuela, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Vietnam, 1964-1975 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Vietnam, 1964-1975 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - West Germany, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - West Germany, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - West Germany, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Yugoslavia, 1967-1976 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Series III. Speaches, Writings, and Reports
  - American Legion, 1963-1968 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Americas Responsibility, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Communism, 1960-1968 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Communism, 1960-1968 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - International Situation, 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Labor Related material, 1961-1968 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - NATO, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - NATO, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Politics (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Soviet Union, 1962-1983 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Student Agitation (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - TUC (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - United Nations (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Series IV. Miscellaneous
  Newspaper and magazine articles, foreign materials, reports
  - Foreign Material, 1957-1965 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Foreign Material, 1965-1969 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Foreign Material, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Foreign Material, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Foreign Material, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Foreign Material, 1973-1980 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Foreign Material, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Foreign Material (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Articles, 1950-1973 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Articles, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Articles, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Articles, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Reports, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Reports, 1951-1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Reports, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Reports, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Reports, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Reports, 1973-1981 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Reports, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Reports (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Reports (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Reports (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Reports (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Reports (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Reports (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Reports (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Reports (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Series V. Personal Paraphenalia
  Stamps, pictures, biographical material
  - Biographical material (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Biographical material (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Biographical material (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Series VI. Financial Documents
  - Financial documents (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Financial documents (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Financial documents (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Financial documents (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - AFL-CIO Free Trade Union News Audit and Report (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO Free Trade Union News Audit and Report, 1964-1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Banks, 1957-1960 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cash Receipts and Disbursements Book, 1960-1966 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Cash Receipts and Disbursements Book, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - E. Borochowicz Expenses, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - E. Borochowicz Expenses, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Expense Book, 1960-1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Financial Reports, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Financial Statements, 1969-1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - India, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Misc. Bills, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Misc. Bills, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Misc. Bills, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Pamphlets; Paid, 1966-1969 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Petty Cash Book, 1958-1964 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Petty Cash Book, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Petty Cash, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Petty Cash, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Philadelphia First National City Bank, 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Phone Numbers and Addresses, 1960-1970 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Printing Bills, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Printing Bills, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 24)